

# LUIS CARLOS PEREZ

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

### CONTACT

+36 30 528 7465 LUISCARLOS3106@GMAIL.COM

# SOCIAL MEDIA

LINKEDIN: WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/I
N/LUISCARLOS-FULLSTACK

FACEBOOK:@LUIS CARLOS PEREZ

INSTAGRAM: @LUISK3106

### PROFILE

During my formative years, I've had the opportunity to live in different countries like Dominican Republic, Hungary and Spain, gaining many assets and experiences including personal growth, global perspective, and multiculturism.

Always passionate about technology and currently graduated from "Ironhack", an intensive learning project specialized in programming. Mastering programming technologies like Node.js, ES6, Express, and HTML & CSS, I belief in constant education development.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **BARISTA**

STARBUCKS | MAR 2016 - JUN 2017

• Bring the best services and experiences to costumers

#### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

TECHO | JUN 2014 - JUL 2014

Build houses for the poor in Guatemala

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **WEB DEVELOPMENT**

IRONHACK MADRID | 2017 - 2017 - TECHNOLOGIES: JAVASCRIPT, HTML5, CSS3 AND THE MEAN STACK

#### MANAGEMENT WITH SPECIALISATION IN ARTS

IBS BUDAPEST | 2015 - 2017

- GAIN KNOWLEDGE OF HISTORY, FUNDING, OWNERSHIP AND CREATION OF ARTS, INCLUDING THE MUSIC INDUSTRY PLUS GENERAL MANAGEMENT ISSUES

#### SKILLS

- JavaScript
- Node.js
- Angular4
- Express.js
- MongoDB

- ES6
- JQuery
- HTML5
- CSS
- Web Development

#### AWARDS

#### **AASCA MUSIC FESTIVAL**

MOST OUTSTANDING GUITAR DUET 2014

## LANGUAGES

- Spanish
- Hungarian

• English